

# Lub Lorry Lamysère

Haitian, single, 27 years old (Full-Stack Software Developer)

Purpose: Developing technologically interesting and cleverly designed applications for the web, computer and mobile. I appreciate having comments on all aspects of a project.

8, rue norgues, Christ-Roi Port-au-Prince (Haiti) +(509) 3874-7485 lublorry.lamysere@code9haiti.com www.code9haiti.com

#### **CURRENT POSITION**

Code9Haiti, at #33, 2e avenue du travail, Turgeau Online teaching – March 2020 – Present

#### **EXPERIENCES**

with **CODELIME**, at #20 rue Gérard de Nerval, FRANCE Remote full-stack developer - *June* 2020 - *January* 2021 Build applications and systems with LDAP technology

with **Wyzdev S.A**, #7, route de Kenscoff, Pétion-Ville **Web & Mobile developer** - *February* 2020 - *April* 2021 Build web & mobile apps (Front-end & Back-end).

with **GVG (Global Voice Group)**, #2 rue Maurepas, Delmas 60 **Front-end web developer -** *January* 2020 - *June* 2020 Building the front-end and improving the UX / UI

# with ESIH (Ecole Supérieure d'Infotronique d'Haïti) & AUF (Agence Universitaire de la Francophonie)

**Web developer -** December 2019 -May 2020

A web platform that highlights the contribution of women to World Heritage.

with **Menkonpa**, at Connecticut

Freelance Software developer – August 2017 – June 2021

E-commerce music platform for local bands and musicians.

#### **EDUCATION**

Ecole Supérieure d'Infotronique d'Haïti (ESIH), 23, 2e ruelle Nazon, Haiti — Computer Science (BCS)

September 2014 - July 2018

College Saint Jean, Cayes Haiti — High School

September 2006 - July 2014

# **LEARNING AND KNOWLEDGE SHARING**

#### Stackoverflow—Moderator, Contributor

Problem solver, moderate the platform to remove irrelevant contents about Python / Django / JavaScript

## **Code9Haiti** — Online/On-site

I own my blog, post tutorials, and teach online programming courses.

# **EXPERTISES AND SKILLS**

Entrepreneurship / Leadership / Teamwork

Back-end Web Development: Python / Django / PHP / Laravel / C# / ASP.NET / NodeJS

Front-end Web Development: Vanilla Javascript / HTML / CSS / VueJS / ReactJS / TypeScript

Mobile Development (iOS & Android): Flutter / Android Studio

Computer Software Development: Java / C++ / Python / C#

Database: PostgreSQL / MySQL / SQLite

Project management: Github / Bitbucket / Jira / SVN

Rest API

## **AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS**

**LekolPam (July 2017 - present)** Project Manager. The project allows both school management & interaction.

Winner of Diagnostik Pitch (July 1st, 2017) I pitched the project LekolPam, won the first prize: \$ 2K

**Code9Haiti - Developer Community (June 2016 - present)** Founder, president & lead developer of the community !?

Winner Hack the CD at Seattle - Washington (June 26th, 2016) I have been awarded Best in Diaspora Award Winner for the web and mobile application LekolPam.

Winner of Haiti Hackfest (May 21,22th, 2016) 1st prize in a Hackathon with a web/mobile application for the school management

#### **LANGUAGES**

Haitian Creole: Native language

French : Fluent English : Fluent

Spanish : High School Notions